In this exercise, you are asked to implement a function that converts
the TF record in the way more open data set format to a different TF record format.
This function takes as input the file name of the original TF record,
an encoded jpeg image in a byte like format,
and the list containing annotations.
First, we need to load the encoded image in
a memory buffer using Python input-output library.
We can then open this image with Pillow and extract the image widths and height.
We use the provided class mapping to map classes name to classes IDs.
Indeed, the way more open data set only contain the classes name.
We then need to convert the annotation in the right format.
In a way more open data sets,
bounding boxes use the center coordinates instead of the corner coordinates.
We convert them to the wanted format by
adding or subtracting half of the lengths and half of the widths.
Multiple bounding boxes format exist and
this is an operation you will have to do pretty frequently.
Finally, we need to create the different protocol messages using the provided functions.
We put these protocol messages into a TF train example.
Because different machine learning libraries require different data formats,
you need to become comfortable converting data from one format to another.